proposable.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy : Proposal Software & Free Proposal Templates : Proposable

##  Information Practices 

Proposable, LLC ("Company") understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to our web site, PROPOSABLE.COM (the "Site") and recognizes our obligation to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you. We may modify this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") at any time and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent. 

##  Collection of Information 

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, address, phone number, email address, county of residence or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that will be used in connection with the Proposable software and/or that is required to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP number (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation. 

##  Use of Information 

We use your Personal Information for the following purposes: for use in connection with the Proposable software; to administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that maybe of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. We may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as sending email messages, managing data or hosting the Site. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other web sites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other web sites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If the Company is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information maybe among the transferred assets. 

##  Retention and Modification of Information 

We retain Personal Information for as long as the information is relevant to our business purposes or until you request that we remove the data by contacting us at [team@proposable.com](mailto:team@proposable.com). If you wish to update your Personal Information provided to us, please visit PROPOSABLE.COM and ask to have data removed through the feedback button. 

##  User Invitations 

You can invite friends to become registered users by sending an invitation email via our automated invitation system. We store the email addresses that you provide so that we may keep track of how many people are being invited. We do not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication. Recipients of invitations may contact us at [team@proposable.com](mailto:team@proposable.com) to request the removal of their information from our database. 

##  Email Communications 

When you send an email to us, you are communicating with Company electronically. You thereby consent to receive communications from Company electronically. Company will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the Site. All agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that Company provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. 

##  Cookies 

When you visit the Site, we may passively collect certain information without your prior consent. Such information (collected in standard web server logs) may include your IP address, browser type, and web access times. Such passively collected information is used in standard web traffic analysis, in conjunction with demographic/aggregate analysis of collected user records. 

We may also collect information through the use of "cookies" which are small computer files that are transferred to a computer's hard drive and which permit us to know about site visits. We may use cookies or similar technology to improve your experience on the Site by making it easier for you to navigate through the Site or to make a Site feature work better. Information collected from a "cookie" might include information regarding your browser, type of computer, operating system, Internet service provider and other similar information. Cookie technology may also gather information about the areas you visit on our Site and about the links you may select from within our Site to other areas of the Internet. 

We do not extract Personal Information during this process. Currently, we use both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to maintain tracking of a user through an application and expire at the end of a web page visit. Persistent cookies do not expire at the end of the session. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive and read by your browser each time you visit the Site. Such cookies contain only a numeric session identifier. We use such information in the aggregate to understand which services and resources our visitors prefer and how those services and resources are used. We may share aggregate demographic/statistical information with third parties. 

With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features. 

##  Links 

YThe Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any third party sites. Therefore, the Company disclaims any liability for any third party's use of your Personal or Anonymous Information obtained through using a third party web site. 

##  Security 

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. 

##  Contacting Proposable 

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us by email at [team@proposable.com](mailto:team@proposable.com) or by postal mail at 300 West Hillside Dr. Bloomington, Indiana 47403. Please provide a concise communication with complete information, including your contact information.
